(Leonard:)But we don't need to quibble
over terminology.
(Lesley:)What sort of experiment
would you propose?
(Leonard:)There is a generally accepted
pattern in this area.
I pick you up, take you to a restaurant,
then we would see a movie.
(Leonard:)Probably a romantic comedy
featuring the talents...
(Leonard:)...of Hugh Grant or Sandra Bullock.
(Lesley:)Interesting.
(Lesley:)And would you agree
the primary way we would evaluate...
(Lesley:)...the success or failure of the date would
be based on the biochemical reaction...
- ...during the good-night kiss?
- Heart rate, pheromones, et cetera, yes.
Why don't we stipulate
the date goes well...
...and move to the key variable?
- You mean kiss you now?
- Yes.
(Leonard:)- Define the parameters of the kiss.
- Closed mouth, but romantic.
(Lesley:)- Mint?
- Thank you.
[MINTS CRACKING]
(Leonard:)- Shall I count down from three?
- No, I think it needs to be spontaneous.